Guide to the Luis Leal Papers, 1946-1985
Department of Special Collections
- Series 6: Reference Materials
  - Subseries B: Luis Leal research folder files on latin america. General, literature, culture. A-Z
    - Teatro hispanoamericano. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Uruguay. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Uslar Pietri, Arturo. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Vallejo, César. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Vargas Llosa, Mario. (cont...) (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Vargas Llosa, Mario. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Venezuela. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Subseries C: Luis Leal research folder files on mexican authors. A-Z
    - Abreu Gómez, E. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Acevedo Escobedo, Antonio. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Acuña, Manuel. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Agustín, José. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Alessio Robles, Vito (y Miguel) (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Altamirano, Ignacio M. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Alva Ixtlilxóchitl. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Alvarez del Castillo, M. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Amor, Guadalupe. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Arellano, Jesús. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Aridjis, Homero. (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Arredondo, Inés. (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Arreola, Juan José. (cont...) (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Arreola, Juan José. (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Avilés Fabila, René. (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Azar, Hector. (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Azuela, Arturo. (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Azuela, Mariano. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Azuela, Mariano - Los de abajo. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Azuela, Mariano - Lectura temática. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Azuela, Mariano - General notes. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Balbuena, Bernardo de. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Banda Farfán, Raquel. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Basurto, Luis G. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Benítez, Fernando. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Bermúdez, M. E. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Blanco, Manuel. (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Bocanegra, Fr. Matías. (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Bulnes, Francisco. (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Bustamante, Carlos M. (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Cabada, Juan de la. (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Camarillo de Pereyra, María Enriqueta. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Campo, Angel de. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Campobello, Nellie. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Campos, Julieta. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Campos, Marco Antonio. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Campos, Rubén M. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Campos Alatorre, C. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Cantón, Wilberto. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Carballido, Emilio. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Carballo, Emmanuel. (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Carrillo y Ancona. (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Castellanos, Rosario. (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Castillo, Florencio M. del. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Carrión, Ulises. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Caso, Antonio. (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Castilo, y Lanzas. (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Ceballos, Ciro B. (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Cervantes de Salazar. (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Córdova, Luis. (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Cortés, Hernán. (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Cosío Villegas. (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Cravioto, Alfonso. (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Cruz, Sor Juana. (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Cruz, Sor Juana - Sainete 2. (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Cuellar, José T. de. (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Cuesta, Jorge. (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Chumacero. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Dávila, Amparo. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Dávila Padilla. (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Delgado, Rafael. (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Díaz del Castillo, B. (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Díaz Dufóo, C. (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Díaz Mirón, Salvador. (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Dolujanoff, Emma. (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Dueñas, Guadalupe. (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Durán, Fr. Diego. (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Elizondo, Salvador. (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Elizondo (Pepe Nava). (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Espejo, Beatriz. (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Estrada, Genaro. (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Fernández, Justino. (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Fernández, Sergio. (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Fernández de Lizardi - Periquillo. (cont...) (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Fernández de Lizardi - Periquillo. (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Frías, Heriberto. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Frías y Soto. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Fuentes, Carlos. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Obras originales. (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Aura. (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Fuentes, Carlos -Las buenas conciencias. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - La cabeza de la hidra. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Cambio de la piel. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Cine. (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Cuentos. (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Cumpleaños. (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Historia y ficción. (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Artemio Cruz. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - La nueva novela. (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - La región más transparente - I (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - La regíon más transparente - II (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Teatro. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Terra nostra. (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Tiempo mexicano. (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Fuentes, Carlos - Zona sagrada. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Galindo, Sergio. (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Gamboa, Federico. (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - García Icazbalceta, Joaquín. (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - García Ponce, Juan. (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - García Saldaña, P. (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - García Terrés, Jaime. (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Gardea, Jesús. (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Garibay, Ricardo. (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Garibay K., Angel M. (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Garizurieta, César. (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Garro, Elena. (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Godoy, Emma. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - González de Eslava. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - González Martínez, E. (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - González Obregón, Luis. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - González Peña, C. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Gorostiza, Celestino. (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Gorostiza, José. (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Granados y Gálvez, José J. (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Guevara, Fr. Miguel de. (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Guillén, Fredo. (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Gutiérrez Cruz, Carlos. (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Gutiérrez de Santa Clara. (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Gutiérrez Nájera, Manuel. (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Guzmán, Humberto. (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Guzmán, Martín Luis. (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Guzmán, Martín Luis - Islas Marías. (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Guzmán, Martín Luis - La sombra del caudillo. (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Henestrosa, Andrés. (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Henríquez Ureña, Pedro. (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Hernández, Efrén. (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Herrera Frimont, Celestino. (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Huerta, Efraín. (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Humboldt, Alexander. (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Ibargüengoitia, Jorge. (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Icaza, Francisco A. de. (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Iduarte, Andrés. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Inclán, Luis G. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Jiménez Rueda, J. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Leñero, Vicente. (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Lira, Miguel N. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - López Páez, Jorge. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - López Portillo y Rojas. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - López Velarde, Ramón. (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - López y Fuentes. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Madero, Francisco I. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Magdaleno, Mauricio. (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Mancisidor, José. (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Manjarrez, Héctor. (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Manterola, Ramón. (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Maples Arce. (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Martínez, J. L. (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Martínez Peñaloza, Porfirio. (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Martínez Sotomayor, José. (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Maximiliano. (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Melo, Juan Vicente. (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Mendoza, Ma. Luisa. (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Mendoza, Vicente T. (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Menéndez, Miguel Angel. (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Mier, Fr. Servando de Teresa de. (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Mojarro, Tomás. (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Mojica, Fr. José Francisco de Guadalupe. (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Molina, Fr. Alonso. (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Montemayor, Carlos. (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Monterde, Francisco. (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Monterroso, Augusto. (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Montes de Oca, Marco Antonio. (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Mora, José Luis. (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Múñoz, Rafael. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Murillo, Gerardo (Dr. Atl) (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Nandino, Elías. (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Navarrete, Manuel. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Navarrete, Raúl. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Nervo, Amado - Cuentos. (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Nervo, Amado - Writings. (cont...) (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Nervo. Amado - Writings. (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Novo, Salvador. (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Ochoa Sandoval, Eglantina. (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Ojeda, Jorge Arturo. (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Ontañón, Eduardo de. (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Ortega, Francisco. (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Ortiz de Montellano, Bernardo. (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Othón, Manuel José. (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Pacheco, José Emilio. Morirás lejos (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Pacheco, José Emilio. (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Pacheco, José Emilio. (cuentos) (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Payno, Manuel. (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Payo del Rosario (Pablo Villavicencio). (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Paz, Ireneo. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Paz, Octavio. (cont...) (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Paz, Octavio. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Paz, Octavio - Tiempo nublado (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Paz, Octavio - La hija de Rappaccini (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Paz, Octavio - Obras originales (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Paz, Octavio - Posdata (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Paz, Octavio - El laberinto de la soledad (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Pellicer, Carlos. (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Peón Contreras, José. (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Pereyra, Carlos. (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Pimentel, Francisco. (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Piña, Juan Izquierdo de (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Pitol, Sergio (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Poniatowska, Elena. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Prieto, Guillermo. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Quintana Roo, Don Andrés. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Rabasa, Emilio. (Sancho Polo) (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Ramírez, Ignacio. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Ramírez, José Fernando. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Revueltas, José. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Reyes, Alfonso. (cont...) (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Reyes, Alfonso. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Reyes, Alfonso - Cuento y novela (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Reyes y Borges. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Reyes y Stern. (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Riestra, Gloria. (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Riva Palacio, Vicente. (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Roa Bárcena, José María. (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Robles, Antonio de. (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Robles, Martha. (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Rodríguez Galván, Ignacio. (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Rojas González, Francisco. (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Romero, José Rubén. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Rosa, Luis de la. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Rosas de Oquendo, Mateo. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Rosas Moreno, José. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Rubín, Ramón. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Ruiz de Alarcón, Juan. (cont...) (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Ruiz de Alarcón, Juan. (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Rulfo, Juan. (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Obras originales (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Biografías y bibliografías (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Entrevistas (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Cuentos (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Crítica, general. (cont...) (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Crítica, general. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Pedro Páramo (cont...) (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Rulfo, Juan - Pedro Páramo (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Rulfo, Juan - El llano en llamas (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Saavedra Guzmán, Antonio de (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Sabines, Jaime. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Sainz, Gustavo. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Salado Alvarez, Victoriano. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Salazar Mallén, Rubén. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Sandoval y Zapata, Luis de (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Santacilia, Pedro. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Santamaría, Francisco J. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Schmidhuber, Guillermo. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Sedano, Francisco. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Segovia, Tomás. (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Sierra, Justo. (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Sigüenza y Góngora, Carlos de (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Silva Y Acenes, Mariano. (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Solana, Rafael. (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Solórzano, Carlos. (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Spota, Luis. (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Tablada, José Juan. (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Terrazas, Francisco de. (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Torres Bodet, Jaime. (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Torri, Julio. (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Tovar, Juan. (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Tovar, Juan de. (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Tovar, Pantaleón. (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Traven, B. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Turrent Rozas, Lorenzo (1903-1941). (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Urbina, Luis G. (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Urquiza, Concha (1910-1945). (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Usigli, Rodolfo. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Valadés, Edmundo. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Valle-Arizpe, Artemio de. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Vasconcelos, José. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Vasconcelos, José - Ulises criollo (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Vigil, José María. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Villalobos, Arias de. (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Villaurrautia, Xavier - Poesia (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Villoro, Luis. (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Yáñez, Agustín - Obras originales (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Yáñez, Agustín - Notes I (cont...) (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Yáñez, Agustín - Notes I (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Yáñez, Agustín - Notes II (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Zarco, Francisco. (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Zea, Leolpoldo. (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Zepeda, Eraclio. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Abad, Manuel. Acal Glisaliturri, Jesús. Acosta, Diego Agustín. Adame, Arturo. Agueros, Victoriano. Aguilar Narváez, José. Aguilar, Rafael. Ajuayo, Miguel. Aldalur, Fr. José Antonio de. Aldone, R. J. Alegre, Francisco Javier. Almazar de Peréz Barrera, María Helena. Alonso Román, Hugo. Alonso de Avila, José. Alvarez, Griselda. Amo, J. Araujo y Escandón, Alejandro. Arguelles, Hugo. Ariceaga, Alejandro. Arjuedos, Lal. Arellano López, Jaime. Arreoloa, José María. Arriola, P. Juan. Augusto, Guillermo. Avellaneda, Andrés O. Azcaráte y Lezame, Juan Francisco. (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Luis Leal research folder files on additional mexican authors. A-Z
    - Barreda, Octavio G. Barrera, Carlos. Basurto, Luis G. Blanco, Joaquín. Bocángel, Grabriel. Bolaños, Fr. Joaquin Bonilla, Fr. Juan de. Borges, Jorge Luis. Borquez, Djed (Juan de Dios Borquez) Broissin Abdalá, Francisco. Burns, Archibaldo. (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Cabrera, Luis G. Calderón de la Barca, Fanny. Calvillo Madrigal,Salvador. Camarillo, María Eriqueta. Cameron, Albert Perry III. Camín, Alfonso. Campos Alvares, Marco Antonio. Capetillo Robles Gil, Manuel. Carballido, Emilio. Cardon, José O. Caro, Andrés P. Caro Meléndez, Mario Alberto. Carrión, Ulises. Caso, Alfonso. Castellanos, Rosano. Castro, Dolores. Castro del Valle, Daniel. Castro Leal, Antonio. Castro Leal, Paloma. Chanero. Ceballos Maldonado, José. Clavigero, D. Francisco Saverio. Contin, Agustín. Conto, José Berbardo. Contreras, Adolfo. Cosío Villegas, Daniel. Cotín, Eduardo. Covarrubias de Ramos, María Guadalupe. Cox, Patricia. Cruz, Sor Juana. Cuenca, Agustín F. Cueva, Hermilo de la. Cuevas, Rafael Cox, Patricia. (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Dallal, Alberto. Daltón, Margarita. Delgado, Antonio. Díaz Mirón, Salvador. Dominguez, Rafael. (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Echeverría, Manuel. Elguero, José. Elízaga, Lorenzo. Erro, Luis Henrique. Espejo, Beatriz. Espinoza de Orellana, Nelly. Estrada, Genaro. Estrella Pérez, Raúl. (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Faríll, Manuel. Fernández, Justino. Fernández Macgregor, Jenaro. Flor Casanova, Noé de la. Flores Aguirre, Jesús. Flores, Manuel M. Fraire, Isabel. Frías, José D. (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Galindo, Aurelio. Gallardo, Amelio Luis. Gamboa de Camino, Berta. Garcia, Antonio. Garcia Jimenez, Juan. Garcia Villalobos, Miguel. Garfias, Pedro. Garibay B., Ricardo. Garrido, Felipe. Garzón Ruiz, Renato. Giral, José. Girónella, Cecilia. Godoy, Jorge de. Gómez Costa, Arturo. Gómez Haro, Eduardo. Gómez Palacio, Marin. Gomis, Anamari. González, Emiliano. González, Raúl Renán. González de Alba, Luis. González Aramburu, Francisco. González Flores, Manuel. González Franco, Patricia. González Pineda, Francisco. Goytortúa, Jesús. Guardia, Miguel. Guevara, Migule de. Guillén, Fedro. Guisa y Azevedo, Jesús. Guzmán, Humberto. (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Hernández, Luisa Josefina. Herreros, Clementina. (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Ibárgüen A., Sergio Ibargüengoitia, Jorge. Icaza, Francisco A. de. Inclán, Federico S. (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Jemeny Moreno, W. Jiménez, Guillermo. Jiménez Farias, Armando. Jiménez Rueda, Julio. (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Lara Barragán, Antonio. León-Portilla, Miguel. Lerin, Manuel. Llach, Leonor. Llano, José de le. Lombardo de Caso, María. López González, Aralia. Lopéz Paez, Jorge. Lopéz Trujillo, Clemente. Lozano, Víctor Miguel. Luquín, Eduardo. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Macín, Francisco J. MacIver, R. Magaña, Sergio. Manjarrey, Héctor. Marroqui, José María. Marroquin Hidalgo, Carlos. Martínez, Luis. Mastretta, Angeles. Mateos, Juan A. Meidaje, Héctor. Mejía, Demetrio. Méndez Plancarte, Gabriel. Millán, María del Carmen. Mojica, José. Mondragón, Magdalena. Monsreal, Agustín. Monterde, Francisco. Moral, Fernando del. Morales Saviñón, Héctor. Moreno Sánchez, Manuel. Moreno Villa, José. Murillo, Josefa. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Nava Alegría, Lucinda. Navarro, Rubén C. Navarro Aceves, Salvador. Nuñez y Domínguez, José de Jesús. Ocampo, María Luisa. Ochoa, Antonio. Ollavani y Ferrari, Enrique de. Ornelas Hernandez, Adolfo. Orozco, Gilberto. Orozco y Berra, Fernando Ortiz, Orlando. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Palavicini, Felix F. Parámo, Roberto. Paz, Martín. Peazza, Luis Guillermo. Peniche, Vallado. Perea, Cocepción. Peréz Martínez, Héctor. Peréz Salazar, Manuel. Peza, Juan de Dios. Pizano y Saucedo, Carlos. Plaza, Antonio. Prieto, Raúl. Puga y Leal, Manuel. Quevedo y Zulueta, Salvador. Quijano, Alejandro. Quintanilla, Luis. Quintero Alvares, Alberto. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Radilla Ludwig, Manuel Ramírez, José Fernando. Ramírez Cabañas, Joaguín. Ramos, Raymundo. Ramos Meza, Ernesto. Reyes, Alicia. Rivas Sainz, Arturo. Rodríguez, Luis Angel. Rodríguez, Ramón. Rodríguez Beltrán, Cayetano. Rodríguez Chicharro, César. Rodríguez Iglesia, Emilio. Rodríguez Lozano, Manuel. Rojas Rosillo, Isaac. Romero, Ana María. Rosas, José. Rubio, José Rafael. (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Sabino, Miguel. Salas Calderón, Gloria. Sánchez, Felipe. Sánchez Esquivel Cámara, Florencio. Sánchez Mayans, Fernando. Sánchez Ramos, Alfonso. Segovia, Tomas. Sierra, Carlos. Sierra, Justo. Sierra Partida, Alfonso. Sigüenza y Góngora, Carlos de. Silva Herzog, Jesús. Solón de Mel. Solórzano, Carlos. Sorondo, Xavier. Sosa, Francisco. Sotomayor, Arturo. Souza, Antonio. Sustaita, Alberto. (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Tablada, José Juan. Teja Zabre, Alfonso. Toscano, Refugio B, de. Toro, Alfonso. Torres, Francisco. Torres Bodet, Jaime. Tovar, Juan. Traven, Bruno. Trueba, Eugenio. (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Uranga, Emilio. Urquezo, Mariano. Urquizo, Francisco L. Urueta, Jesús. Usigli, Alejandro. Valades, Edmundo. Valdés, Carlos. Valle, Rafeal Heliodoro Vargas Pardo, Xavier. Vazques Santa Ana, Higinio. Velázquez Cárdenas de León, Joaquin. Virchez, Alfonso (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Ximénez. Xoran, Ramón. (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - 10 Yunes, José Luis. Zaid, Gabriel. Zaragoza, Antonio. Zárate, Eduardo E. Zárrage, Angel. Zavala, Lorenzo. Zavala, Silvio. Zayos Enríquez, Rafael de. Zentella, Arcadio. Zetterling, Mai. Zurita Campos, César Eugenio. (Box Box, Folder Folder)
  - Subseries E: Luis Leal research folder files on additional latin american authors. A-Z
    - Aguilar Chavez, Manuel. Aguilera Mata, Demetrio. Aguirre, Margarita. Agustine, Delmira. Airo, Clemente. Albamonte, Luis María. Alegría, Fernando. Allende, Isabel. Amorim, Enrique. Anderson-Imbert, Enrique. Arciniegas, Gabriela. Arciniegas, Germán. Arguedas, José María. Arlt, Roberto. Arraiíz, Antonio. Arrieta, Rafael Alberto. Asturias, Miguel Angel. (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Ballagas, Emilio. Balmaceda Toro, Pedro. Balseiro, José Agustín. Barba-Jacob, Porfirio. Barletta, Leonídas. Barrios, Andrés Antonio. Bartlow Martin, John. Batros Montifor, José. Bécquer, Gustavo Adolfo. Beingolea, Manuel. Belaval, Emilio S. Bello, Andrés. Bianco, José. Blanco-Fombona, Rufus. Bombal, María Luisa. Borges, José Luis. Bosch, Juan. Brull, Mariano. Brunet, Marta. (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Caballero Calderón, Eduardo. Cardenal, Ernesto. Cardénas Peña, José. Cardona Peña, Alfredo. Cardoso, José Aurelio. Caro, Néstor. Caro, José Eusebio. Caro, Miguel Antonio. Carpentier, Alejio. Carranza, Eduardo. Carrasquilla, Tómas. Carrera Andrade, Jorge. Carriego, Evaristo. Carrillo Meza, Raúl. Cartasegna, Rolando. Casaccia, Gabriel. Casey, C. Castellanos, José. Castillo, Abelardo. Castillo, Sor Francisca de la Concepcíon de. Castro, Oscar. Caviedes. Chacón, Tranquilino. Chiapponi, Atilio. Chocano, José Santos. Cerruto, Oscar. Coel, Pedro E. Collado Martell, Alferdo. Congrains M. Enrique. Cuadra, José de la. Cuadra, Pablo Antonio. (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Darío, Rubén. Denevi, Marco. D'Halmar, Augusto. Díaz de Medina, Fernando. Díaz Garcés, Joaquin. Díaz Rodríguez, Manuel. Diego, Eliseo. Donoso, José. Droguett, Carlos. Durand, Luis. (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Echeverría, Esteban. Eguren, José María. Espejo, Angel C. Espejo, Eugenio. Espronceda, José de. Estrella, Guillermo. Euzina, Juan del. (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Fallon, Carlos. Fernández,Roberto G. Fernández Madris, José. Ferrer, S. Flont, Eugenio. (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Gambaro, Griselda. García Calderón, Ventura. Gardeazábal, Alvarez. Garita, Juan. Garmendia, Julio. Gerchunoff, Alberto. Giardinelli, Mempo. Girri, Alberto. Gómez Carrillo, Enrique. González León, Adriano. González León, Salmodiante. González, Joaquín V. González, José Luis. González Prada, Manuel. González Zeledón, Manuel. Greiff, León de. Guaramato, Oscar. Gudiño Kieffer, Eduardo. Guerrero Estrada, Guillermo. Guillot, Victor Juan. Guilte, Nicolas. Gutiérrez, Joaquín. (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Harss, Luis. Heinemans. Heredia, J. M. Hernández Catá, Alfonso. Herrera, Flavio. Herrera y Reissig, Julio. Hurtado, Ramón. (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Ibarzábal, Federico de. Ibarbourou, Juana de. Iglesías, Eugenio Julio. (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Jaimes Freyre, Ricardo. Korn, Alejandro. (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Lafourcade, Enrique. Leyva, Carmen. (María Isabel Carvajal) Lillo, Baldomero. López, A. López, Luis Carlos. Lynd, Benito. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Maluenda, Rafael. Mañade, Jorge. Mármol, José. Marcos, Miguel de. Marqués, René. Mejía Sanchez, Ernesto. Mejía Vallejo, Manuel. Méndez, Francisco. Méndez Calzada, Enrique. Mendoza, Plinio Apuleyo. Meneses, Guillermo. Mera, J. L. Meyer, Mary E. Milanés, José Jacinto. Montaner, Carlos Alberto. Monte, Domingo del. Monteforte Toledo, Mario. Montenegro, Ernesto. Montero Lacasa, Jorge. Montiel Ballesteros, Adolfo. Moyano, Daniel. Mujica-Lainez, Manuel. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Naté Roxlo, Conrado. Neruda, Pablo. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Olavide, Pablo de. Omego Luco, Luis. Otero L., Miguel. Oyarzún, Kemy. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Padrón, Julían. Pareja Diezcanseco, Alfredo. Parra, Angel. Parra, Manuel de la. Paysó, Raúl L. Peralta, B. Perón Salas, Mariano. Pocaterra, José Rafael. Pesante, Edgardo A. Pombo, Rafael. Prieto, Jenaro. Proust, Marcel. Puig, Manuel. (Box 100, Folder 5)